<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>internet on Grathwohl.me</title>
    <link>http://example.org/categories/internet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in internet on Grathwohl.me</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 16:31:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/internet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Big Tech Censorship Is Net Neutrality 2.0</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2021-02-25-censorship/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 16:31:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2021-02-25-censorship/</guid>
      <description>Ever since a plurality of Americans indicated their support for net neutrality circa 2008, a common refrain has been propagated, that leaving ISPs unchecked could usher in a new kind of restricted and censored internet.
Proponents of net neutrality in the United States indicate that their support stems from their fears that ISPs will behave badly, and that we will all suffer as a result.
It was suggested that without net neutrality, nothing would stop companies from offering privileged access to certain web services at the expense of others, stifling free speech and competition in the web technology space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musicians: Want Money? Release For Free.</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2020-09-22-free-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 09:26:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2020-09-22-free-music/</guid>
      <description>Caesars don&amp;rsquo;t fear the pirate.
 For 24 years, the song (Don&amp;rsquo;t Fear) The Reaper by the band, Blue Öyster Cult, was nothing more than a rock n&#39; roll smash hit with countless hours of radio play. It put the band on the map and made them rich. The album that featured the song initially, Agents of Fortune, went platinum in the US, meaning it sold at least 1,000,000 copies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musicians: Want Money? Do Work.</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2020-09-21-music-revenues/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 12:14:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2020-09-21-music-revenues/</guid>
      <description>Musicians everywhere want more - and they want it yesterday. But the answer has been here for two decades.
 Musicians are complaining about the raw deals they are getting from streaming. That&amp;rsquo;s no surprise to anybody who has dealt with &amp;ldquo;DSPs&amp;rdquo; such as Spotify, Apple Music, and Deezer. Anyone who&amp;rsquo;s dealt with these services knows what little actual revenue they can expect to receive. However, isn&amp;rsquo;t it curious that all three of these companies also operate in the podcasting realm, where these kinds of complaints are rarely ever heard?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Browser-Based Audio Metering With the Web Audio API</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2020-08-14-web-audio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2020-08-14-web-audio/</guid>
      <description>How to drive your user interface with browser-based audio analysis
 The browser has gotten surprisingly good at processing real-time audio FFTs, thanks to the Web Audio API. As a result, incredible dynamic musical interfaces are now very achievable on the modern web, and it&amp;rsquo;s a heck of a lot easier than most developer resources would have you believe.
Above is a screengrab from my musical homepage, Multipli.city. There, I host all of my music from over the last ten years for free streaming and lossless download.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
