<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>linux on Grathwohl.me</title>
    <link>/categories/linux/</link>
    <description>Recent content in linux on Grathwohl.me</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/linux/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Working with RTSP in FFmpeg</title>
      <link>/posts/2020-06-23-rtsp-ffmpeg/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2020-06-23-rtsp-ffmpeg/</guid>
      <description>Recently, I&amp;rsquo;ve found myself situated among a great fireworks battle in Brooklyn, NY. As we continue to work out the details about the heightened fireworks activity across the United States, I felt it was important that I document and share my experience to contribute what I can to the ongoing conversation. So, I grabbed an old IP camera I had in a corner gathering dust, placed it outside on my fire escape, and fired it up to get a decent shot of the night sky in my neighborhood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Audio Mastering Workflow for Linux</title>
      <link>/posts/2019-05-05-linuxmasteringflow_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2019-05-05-linuxmasteringflow_1/</guid>
      <description>This series of posts will detail the audio mastering workflow I employ on my main Linux workstation:
   Watercooled Full ATX Tower Intel i9 @ 4.2Ghz 64GB ECC RAM Arch Linux with the linux-rt kernel patches RME HDSPe MADI PCI-X Interface RME Babyface Pro USB Audio Interface   Why? The answer is simple: Linux provides the best audio engineering workflow for audio professionals - hands down. Don&amp;rsquo;t believe me?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Playing Your Audible Audiobooks In Linux</title>
      <link>/posts/2018-09-10-audibleffmpeg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2018-09-10-audibleffmpeg/</guid>
      <description>If you want to convert an Audible .aax file into a less restrictive file format, you can do so with ease using FFmpeg, one of my all-time favorite GPL projects.
Navigate to the directory where the .aax file is that you’d like to test on, and perform the following on the command line:
ffmpeg -activation_bytes 1CEB00DA -i test.aax -vn -c:a copy output.mp4 Doing this creates an mp4 container with only an AAC audio stream inside.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
